<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>No Silo on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in No Silo on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Open Handbook</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/open-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/open-handbook/</guid>
      <description>The Open Handbook The Open Handbook&#xA;The Open Handbook project is a free, open-source reference handbook that introduces students to the conventions of academic writing and research. If you would like to collaborate on the project or have a correction, please contact me. If you know your way around git, you can fork the project on GitHub.&#xA;Table of Contents i. Preface ii. License iii. Acknowledgements iv. Donations Annotation &amp;amp; Critical Reading Critical Notes Audience The Joy of Reuse (Save Your Work) What is Good Writing?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 2 Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and articulating responses to them in the form of essays. Shorter writing assignments will focus on a number of skills that are important for taking part in academic conversations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3X5 Manifesto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/3x5-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/3x5-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>NO SILO &gt; PROJECT GRAIN ELEVATOR &gt; ANALYSIS CARDS 1.0&#xA;1). LIST ALL ARGUMENTS: Identify each argument made in the reading. You might choose a certain symbol to flag arguments during your reading and textual annotations. You might use the letter A, for example. One of the main skills required here is the ability to distinguish assertions and claims (arguments) from the things that support them: examples, metaphors, and evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-of-term Reflection and Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/quarterly-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/quarterly-review/</guid>
      <description>Fall Reflection and Review This assignment takes the place of a final exam and asks you to reflect on all of your work this term. The reflections and self-evaluations you perform here will largely determine your final grade. Please write down your responses and keep them in a safe place&amp;mdash;they will be used in a conference during the first week of classes this winter term.&#xA;My rationale for this assignment is explained somewhat in question #6 in the FAQ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-of-term Reflection and Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/quarterly-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/quarterly-review/</guid>
      <description>Winter Reflection and Review I. Review your participation How many classes or TA sessions did you miss? How engaged were you in the class? Did you complete each of the 8 assigned lectures/workshops? Were your drafts completed and turned in on time? Did you give your best effort on each assignment? How much of the reading did you complete? Did you watch all of the films and prepare for discussion? How much did you contribute to Hive?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essay Assignments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/new_essays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/new_essays/</guid>
      <description>Essay Assignments Essay 1 Re-read Nicholson Baker&amp;rsquo;s essay &amp;ldquo;Changes of Mind&amp;rdquo; and perform a &amp;ldquo;close reading&amp;rdquo; of this object to generate observations that lead to a difficulty or problematic in the interpretation of this object, making sure to ground your observations in an interpretive context. Develop and advance an idea or argument that originates from the identified interpretive difficulty or problematic.&#xA;Essay Requirements: 1,200 to 1,500 words in length. Use the MLA format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essay One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1: Argument Prompt What is education? What is its purpose? Write an essay exploring these questions.&#xA;No more than 3 pages Use the MLA format Special requirements Perform no research for this essay. Do not seek help: no googling; no library visits; don’t ask your uncle, friends, or roommate; no ChatGPT. Just use your head and write what you think in the best way you know how. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry: you are going to do great!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essay Three</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</guid>
      <description>Essay Three: Theoretical Analysis Prompt Max Fischer has an insatiable appetite for extracurricular activities: fencing, bee-keeping, yankee racers, calligraphy, backgammon, theater, and on and on and on. These projects and clubs are forms of self-improvement&amp;mdash;kinds of sovereign inquiry&amp;mdash;but they completely dwarf his responsibilities in the traditional disciplines of formal education: geometry, history, English, etc. According to Dr. Guggenheim, Max is &amp;ldquo;one of the worst students&amp;rdquo; at Rushmore Academy.&#xA;But what might Paulo Freire argue about Max&amp;rsquo;s behavior as a human being and a scholar?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essay Two</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</guid>
      <description>Essay Two: Synthesis Prompt Percy and Freire, each in their own way, ask us to consider the problem of authority that attends educational systems or the experience of learning. Write an essay that synthesizes their thinking, explaining how they both investigate the nature of this problem, examine its consequences, and offer solutions.&#xA;Use the MLA format On Synthesis As the name suggests, synthesis essays focus on combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments or ideas relate to one another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the Post-Apocalyptic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/post-apocalyptic-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/post-apocalyptic-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Ideas on the (Post)Apocalyptic The post-apocalyptic narrative is a fantasy or species of wish-fulfillment that expresses a desire for the end of civilization as we know it. The popularity of such films and novels suggest a range of audience responses and psychological conditions behind this wish: Economic despair and disempowering socio-economic structuring lead to a fanciful embrace of post-apocalyptic narrative as a balm, compensation, a comfort. We imagine a future where all systems of power, all hierarchies of values, all bureaucracies and governing institutions are utterly leveled, creating a landscape of pure possibility where anything is possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus-revised/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Syllabus Writing 2: Education and Authority Course Description Writing 2-3 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts, discussing them together, and composing responses to them in the form of essays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Syllabus Writing 2: Education and Authority Course Description Writing 2-3 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts, discussing them together, and composing responses to them in the form of essays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing 3: Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w21/</guid>
      <description>Post-apocalyptic Fiction, Film, and Art Course Description Why do we feel such an attraction to disaster? Why do we produce novels, films, and other forms of art that contemplate the end of humanity? Scholars from many disciplines have offered theories about the appeal and meaning of such spectacles of apocalyptic destruction. We will read some of this critical literature, examining views from disciplines such as psychology, sociology, cultural studies, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing 3: Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w22/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Syllabus Post-apocalyptic Fiction, Film, and Art Course Description Why do we feel such an attraction to disaster? Why do we produce novels, films, and other forms of art that contemplate the end of humanity? Scholars from many disciplines have offered theories about the appeal and meaning of such spectacles of apocalyptic destruction. We will read some of this critical literature, examining views from disciplines such as psychology, sociology, cultural studies, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing 3: Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Syllabus Post-apocalyptic Fiction, Film, and Art Course Description Why do we feel such an attraction to disaster? Why do we produce novels, films, and other forms of art that contemplate the end of humanity? Scholars from many disciplines have offered theories about the appeal and meaning of such spectacles of apocalyptic destruction. We will read some of this critical literature, examining views from disciplines such as psychology, sociology, cultural studies, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Hive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/hive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/hive/</guid>
      <description>What is Hive? Hive is an open-source repository containing notes, ideas, and questions about our course readings and class discussions. We will build this resource together as a class&amp;mdash;sharing the work of interpreting, analyzing, and questioning the complex course readings we encounter. The &amp;ldquo;hive mind&amp;rdquo; is capable of discovering far more than any one individual. With luck, Hive will become a central resource in our class discussions and an indispensable aid to you as you craft your essays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 3 Writing 3 focuses on academic research writing. Our libraries have an impressive array of traditional and electronic search tools as well as millions of books, journal articles, and assorted media. Although navigating this vast sea of information is intimidating, it is important that you find your way: excellent research skills are fundamental to your undergraduate training, regardless of your chosen field of study. In consideration of its importance, we will spend a significant amount of time learning how to use our library effectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author Page Example</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/author-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/author-page/</guid>
      <description>This is a mockup of an Author Page for a research project. Use this as a template for your own project. Create your own Author Page as a Google doc; or, if you prefer, you may use the Journeys WordPress platform. Put a link to your project on our course research projects page. Alan Taylor Revanchist Masculinity in Recent Post-Apocalyptic Cinema This paper examines a strain of post-apocalyptic narrative featuring what we may call “revanchist masculinity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/reading-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/reading-notes/</guid>
      <description>Disaster, Apocalypse, and the State of Nature Reading Notes Thomas Hobbes, Leviathan (1651) Men are essentially equal when all is “reckoned together.” Equal in power, equal in common sense or wisdom. We might think that we are smarter than others, but we are mostly the same. This sense of equality leads to three causes of &amp;ldquo;quarrel&amp;rdquo;:&#xA;COMPETITION: Because we know ourselves to be equals, we become hopeful of attaining ends, goals, possessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stills from Night of the Living Dead</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/night-stills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/night-stills/</guid>
      <description>Stills from Night of the Living Dead (1968) Review of Night of the Living Dead by film critic Roger Ebert (1969): &amp;ldquo;The kids in the audience were stunned. There was almost complete silence. The movie had stopped being delightfully scary about halfway through, and had become unexpectedly terrifying. There was a little girl across the aisle from me, maybe nine years old, who was sitting very still in her seat and crying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stills from The Last Man</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/last-man-stills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/writing-3/last-man-stills/</guid>
      <description>The Last Man (1964) The Last Man on Earth appeared in 1964 and stars the incomparable Vincent Price. The film is the first adaptation of the 1954 novel I Am Legend by Richard Matheson. As you may know, the film was remade again in 2007 with Will Smith (who does much more than slap people in the film). We will view both of these films and I think it is helpful to try and compare them and note how the films evolve between the two historical moments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; FAQs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/FAQs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/FAQs/</guid>
      <description>Course FAQs 1. May I email you my essay for extra comments? No. I always give each essay draft a full set of written comments. And I&amp;rsquo;m committed to meet with any student who would like to go over them as many times as necessary. However, I usually do not take requests for extra comments via email unless there is no other possible way a student can meet with me in an office hour or at some other scheduled time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Evaluating</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/on-evaluating/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:54:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/on-evaluating/</guid>
      <description>My department recently opened a dialogue about grading. This reminded me of a classic Peter Elbow essay entitled &amp;ldquo;Ranking, Evaluating, Liking: Sorting Out Three forms of Judgment.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;In one key passage, Elbow argues that too much of an emphasis on evaluation disrupts learning:&#xA;Most important of all, evaluation harms the climate for learning and teaching&amp;mdash;or rather too much evaluation has this effect. That is, if we evaluate everything students write, they tend to remain tangled up in the assumption that their whole job in school is to give teachers &amp;ldquo;what they want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Bio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/bio/</guid>
      <description>Alan C. Taylor I grew up on a mountain swallowed up by kudzu just across the river from Chattanooga, Tennessee.&#xA;In college and graduate school I studied nineteenth-century American literature, culture, and history. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in backcountry settlements in the early republic and conflicts between Native peoples and settlers.&#xA;I teach writing and research at Dartmouth College.&#xA;I wrote The Open Handbook&amp;mdash;a free, open-source reference book that introduces students to the conventions of academic writing and research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Write me PGP | PGP Fingerprint:&#xA;A14D 400A 810B CB92 F903&#xA;8773 035F 719F 2B4C 40F0&#xA;Office hours MWF 2-3 Or by appointment What are office hours?&#xA;Office location 37 Dewey Field Road, room 224.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Field Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/project-grain-elevator/field-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/project-grain-elevator/field-notes/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;Our field-records will be perhaps the most valuable of all our results; hence the importance of a convenient system of record.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;— Joseph Grinnell, 1908&#xA;Field Notes The central metaphor for this course is the field note. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Thought Machines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/project-grain-elevator/thought-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/project-grain-elevator/thought-machines/</guid>
      <description>Thought Machines Thought machines are tiny mechanisms designed to help us think. Some provoke our thinking by directing our attention to texts or artifacts in certain specific ways. This might help us notice certain features that had previously escaped our view. Some may help us as we write to deepen our analysis by prompting a more systematic approach to the analysis. And while these tools may be used on written texts, many of them are useful for examining other cultural objects such as film, music, art, and many other forms of cultural artifacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Altering Sources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops Altering sources Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. However, doing so is rarely a simple process of cutting and pasting the words from a source into your own document. Instead, you will routinely encounter challenges during the quotation of a source that threaten the clarity and correctness of your prose. For example:&#xA;What do you do when you are writing in the present tense and the source material you are quoting uses the past tense?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annotation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/annotation/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops Annotation In college you will encounter demanding texts of great complexity. You will be asked to engage these texts critically and to challenge the thinking and conclusions of others. You will also have to retain an extraordinary amount of information and recall it later. To thrive in this environment you will need to develop some new habits and strategies. The most basic, and most fundamental, of these is a formal procedure for the annotation of texts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argument Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops Argument Analysis Analysis involves breaking an argument down into smaller parts so that you can understand how those parts work together to make the whole (or fail to do so). During this class we will try to train our minds to uncover the argumentative structure of all that we read.&#xA;Workshop Relying on your annotations and critical notes, construct an outline of the argument found in Nicholson Baker&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Changes of Mind&amp;rdquo; essay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argument Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops Argument Summary In a summary you present the ideas of another writer in condensed form. The length of a summary is dictated by your rhetorical needs, but they are always shorter than the original text. For example, the summary of a large book could be 20 pages, one paragraph, or one sentence. Although a summary sacrifices specificity and detail in the interest of brevity, it must always remain a faithful representation of the original text&amp;rsquo;s meaning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argument Synthesis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Synthesis What is synthesis? As the name suggests, synthesis involves combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments relate to each another.&#xA;To begin a synthesis, ask yourself these (and similar) questions about the readings you plan to synthesize:&#xA;What issues, topics, or problems do the source materials have in common? Are the arguments similar, or do they differ in some respects?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibliographic Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/bibliographic-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/bibliographic-management/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Bibliographic Management Most of us take a very shortsighted approach to our work. We take notes. We do the readings. We complete the assignments. We turn in our work and receive our grade. But then we just move on. All the work product from our labors and the materials we used for learning are abandoned; ultimately, they cross the event horizon into the black hole of a computer hard drive, never to emerge again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutting Corners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/cutting-corners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/cutting-corners/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Cutting Corners in Research I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you the number of times a first-year student has waited until the other students left the classroom in order to approach me and sheepishly ask this question: &amp;ldquo;Professor, if I get a book from the library or download an article for my research project, do I have to read the whole thing?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Don&amp;rsquo;t be silly; of course not.&#xA;And I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you a secret: professors don&amp;rsquo;t read everything in their field(s) of study either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding a Book in the Library</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/locate-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/locate-books/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Finding a Book in the Library Finding a book (or other physical resource) on the shelf of the library isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as it sounds. This is a guide to help you understand how libraries are organized and find books you need for your research.&#xA;Library Classification Systems Libraries use classification systems to organize their holdings. The most common in the English-speaking world are the Dewey Decimal Classification (DDC) and the Library of Congress Classification (LCC) systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Periodicals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/find-periodicals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/find-periodicals/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Finding Periodicals &amp;amp; Electronic Databases Periodicals are publications that are published at regular intervals, such as scholarly journals, magazines, and newspapers. Examining periodicals&amp;mdash;especially academic journals&amp;mdash;is an important aspect of research. Since books often take a year or more to go through the process of peer review, editing, typesetting, and printing before they become available for purchase, they often do not contain the most current information. Articles, on the other hand, appear in a far shorter period of time and generally contain the most up-to-date research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Books/Articles We Don&#39;t Own</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/inter-library-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/inter-library-loan/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Getting Sh*t the Library Doesn&amp;rsquo;t Have A common problem in academic research is discovering that a book or article you require for a project is checked out, missing, or not owned by the library. Less commonly, you may find yourself in a global pandemic and be unable to physically visit a library to borrow books. There are a number of free services available to you when you encounter this problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Academic Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/academic-research-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/academic-research-intro/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Introduction to Academic Research &amp;ldquo;The problem is that doing scholarly work is intrinsically a mess.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;mdash; Kieran Healy&#xA;Perhaps the most common feature of books designed to help students do academic research is their dishonesty. These textbooks present academic research as an orderly list of procedures and tasks, each one leading logically to the next, culminating in a superbly crafted essay. This narrative generally begins with the formulation of a research question, proceeds to the gathering of background information and secondary sources, and finally to the drafting, revision, and completion of the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Cultural Studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/cultural-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/cultural-studies/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Introduction to Cultural Studies This class will frequently use a mode of analysis associated with cultural studies. This lecture provides a brief introduction to this form of inquiry. Listen to the lecture below and afterward examine the example analysis of The Dark Knight (2008).&#xA;Further reading and citations: Completely optional further reading on cultural studies and related concepts: &amp;ldquo;Cultural Studies,&amp;rdquo;, by Dan Kagan; &amp;ldquo;Articulation Theory,&amp;rdquo; by Jennifer Daryl Slack; and &amp;ldquo;Cultural Materialism,&amp;rdquo; by Macdonald Daly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Introductions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/introductions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/introductions/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops On Introductions Writing a good introduction is like asking someone out on a date. You’ve got to make a good first impression, it’s helpful if you look good, and if the other person just can’t see where this is going, you’re probably going to get turned down cold. In short, introduction is seduction.&#xA;Many of the introductions I’ve read, while competent and informative, are not very seductive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Sentence Variety</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Sentence Variety Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. Student writers are often able to write sentences well in their own voice but have difficulty when they try to weave the voices of others into their prose. I also find that most students have developed a particular strategy or formula for quotation that they use over and over again as a kind of crutch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching with Precision</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/search-with-precision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/search-with-precision/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Searching with Precision This workshop is designed to help you perform keyword searches of library catalogs and electronic databases with efficiency. While most students have some familiarity with keyword searching through the Google search engine, library catalogs and databases don&amp;rsquo;t work in the same way. To query databases effectively and efficiently, you need to be familiar with Boolean searches.&#xA;Keyword searches often produce too many results to examine in a reasonable amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showing, not Telling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/show-not-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/show-not-tell/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Show, Don&amp;rsquo;t Tell In writing that involves outside sources it is often more powerful to show rather than tell. But what does that mean?&#xA;While it is an important and necessary skill to summarize or paraphrase the words of other writers using our own words, relying exclusively on this strategy may give your readers reasons to doubt your presentation of the facts. You are, in essence, telling your readers: &amp;ldquo;Just trust me, this is accurate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student Peer Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops Peer Review Work Reflective Prologue Take a moment to reflect on your work. Consider the following questions and write answers to them at the conclusion of your essay draft. Please ensure that this reflective work appears in the essay draft you turn in to Canvas as well.&#xA;What did you learn by writing this draft? What was the most challenging thing about creating this draft? What do you like most about this draft?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical Argument</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/theoretical-argument/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/theoretical-argument/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops Theoretical Argument Source Text Student Paragraph Rushmore the school tries to keep Max under control, but Max resists it. Max has terrible grades, even in Theater II, a class which you would think he would excel at. But why is Max failing all of his classes when he is clearly very intelligent? It is clear that Max is far more interested in his many extracurricular activities than in the traditional classroom lessons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Peer Review?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/peer-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/peer-reviews/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Peer review Peer review is a form of quality control in academic publishing. Before books or articles are published, they experience a rigorous process of evaluation by at least three experts who have advanced training in the field of study in question. These &amp;ldquo;referees,&amp;rdquo; as they are known, review the work anonymously. This anonymity theoretically ensures a more honest appraisal of the work under consideration for publication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with Sources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/working-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/working-sources/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops Working with Sources Documentation, quotation, summary, paraphrase Perhaps the most challenging aspect of academic writing is the integration of source materials. Students often imagine that the most difficult thing about using sources is learning how and when to use a citation. While accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry, citing the page number of a source is not the only skill that is required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Works Cited / Bibliography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/chicago-bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/chicago-bibliography/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Works Cited or Bibliography Accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry. If you fail to properly document your sources, your readers will be unable to follow your research, validate your claims, or judge the quality of your argument. Furthermore, failing to properly cite a source (whether summarized, paraphrased, or quoted) opens you to the charge of plagiarism, a serious academic offense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Works Cited / Bibliography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/mla-bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/courses/workshops/mla-bibliography/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops Works Cited or Bibliography Accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry. If you fail to properly document your sources, your readers will be unable to follow your research, validate your claims, or judge the quality of your argument. Furthermore, failing to properly cite a source (whether summarized, paraphrased, or quoted) opens you to the charge of plagiarism, a serious academic offense.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
