<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I. Preface</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/preface/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/preface/</guid>
      <description>Preface College students are commonly required to purchase handbooks for use in their writing courses. These reference texts introduce students to the conventions of academic writing and often include chapters on academic research, critical thinking, grammar, and formal citation.
The knowledge contained in these texts is indispensable. However, most handbooks on the market today are bloated in both content and price (I think the former is often the justification for the latter).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/license/</guid>
      <description>License This work is licensed under a Creative Commons license.
      CC BY-NC-SA 4.0
You are free to share (copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format) and adapt (remix, transform, and build upon the material) under the terms set out in the international license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 2</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 2  Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and articulating responses to them in the form of essays. Shorter writing assignments will focus on a number of skills that are important for taking part in academic conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay One</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1: Argument  What is education? What is its purpose? Write an essay exploring these questions.
Format and length  No more than 3 pages Use the MLA format  Special requirement Do not perform any research for this essay. No googling. No library visits. Don’t ask your uncle, friends, or roommate. Just use your head and write what you think.
  Submit this assignment to Canvas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay Three</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</guid>
      <description>Essay Three: Theoretical Analysis  In Rushmore, Max Fischer has an insatiable appetite for extracurricular activities: fencing, bee-keeping, yankee racers, calligraphy, backgammon, theater, and on and on and on. These projects and clubs are forms of self-improvement&amp;mdash;kinds of sovereign inquiry&amp;mdash;but they completely dwarf his responsibilities in the traditional disciplines of formal education: geometry, history, English, etc. According to Dr. Guggenheim, Max is &amp;ldquo;one of the worst students&amp;rdquo; at Rushmore Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay Two</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</guid>
      <description>Essay Two: Synthesis  Percy and Freire, each in their own way, ask us to consider the problem of authority within educational systems or experiences. Write an essay that synthesizes their thinking, explaining how they both investigate the nature of this problem, examine its consequences, and offer solutions.
As the name suggests, synthesis essays focus on combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments or ideas relate to one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>II. Donations</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/donations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/donations/</guid>
      <description>Donations Students who would like to make a small gift in honor of this project are encouraged to make electronic donations to the New Hampshire Food Bank, a nonprofit organization that feeds other Granite Staters in need.
 Every $1 you donate provides two meals to someone who can&#39;t afford one.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Meet Your Professor   
Writing 2: What is Education? Course Description Prof&#39;s Current Jam 1  Prof&#39;s Current Jam 2  --- Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and articulating responses to them in the form of essays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Hive</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/hive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/hive/</guid>
      <description>What is Hive? Hive is an open-source repository containing notes, ideas, and questions about our course readings and class discussions. We will build this resource together as a class&amp;mdash;sharing the work of interpreting, analyzing, and questioning the complex course readings we encounter. The &amp;ldquo;hive mind&amp;rdquo; is capable of discovering far more than any one individual. With luck, Hive will become a central resource in our class discussions and an indispensable aid to you as you craft your essays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 3</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 3  Writing 3 focuses on academic research writing. Our libraries have an impressive array of traditional and electronic search tools as well as millions of books, journal articles, and assorted media. Although navigating this vast sea of information is intimidating, it is important that you find your way: excellent research skills are fundamental to your undergraduate training, regardless of your chosen field of study. In consideration of its importance, we will spend a significant amount of time learning how to use our library effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annotation &amp; Critical Reading</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Annotation and Critical Reading   &amp;ldquo;There is something predatory, cruel even, about a pen suspended over a text. Like a hawk over a field, it is on the lookout for something vulnerable. Then it is a pleasure to swoop and skewer the victim with the nib&amp;rsquo;s sharp point. The mere fact of holding the hand poised for action changes our attitude to the text. We are no longer passive consumers of a monologue but active participants in a dialogue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Critical Notes</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Critical Notes   &amp;ldquo;We believe the best way to work on a difficult text is by rereading . . . but you can also work on the difficult text by writing, by taking possession of the work through sentences and paragraphs of your own, through summary, paraphrase, and quotation, by making another writer&amp;rsquo;s work part of your work&amp;rdquo; (12).
&amp;mdash; Bartholomae and Petrosky, &amp;ldquo;Introduction.&amp;rdquo; Ways of Reading: An Anthology for Writers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audience</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Audience   &amp;ldquo;[A] work of rhetoric is pragmatic; it comes into existence for the sake of something beyond itself; it functions ultimately to produce action or change in the world; it performs some task. In short, rhetoric is a mode of altering reality, not by the direct application of energy to objects, but by the creation of discourse which changes reality through the mediation of thought and action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Reuse (Save Your Work)</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>The Joy of Reuse  Save all your work Most students complete their school work, turn it in to their professor, then never think of it again. These efforts then cross the event horizon into the black hole of a computer hard drive, never to emerge again. If this sounds like your standard practice, consider a change now that you&amp;rsquo;ve arrived at college. When you write something (essays, notes, reports, projects, code), or when you use something (course readings, research, data), keep a copy of it in some organized folder system so you may return to it in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. What is Good Writing?</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>What is Good Writing?  Academic writing takes many forms. However, all good academic writing shares several basic characteristics:
  Good academic writing always contains a strong thesis statement: an idea, stated as an assertion, that is the work&amp;rsquo;s central focus.
  Good academic writing is organized: each paragraph builds upon the one before it, creating a strong sense of purpose. The paragraphs themselves are unified, generally pursuing a single idea that helps support the thesis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Types of College Writing</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Types of College Writing  Most students are trained in high school to write what is known as a five-paragraph essay&amp;mdash;a form of writing containing an introduction, three paragraphs of support, and a summary conclusion. In that it encourages students to think about introductions, structure, organization, paragraphing, evidence, and reasoning, the five-paragraph essay is good training for novice writers. However, this particular rhetorical form is extremely limiting: only certain, rather paltry, thoughts and ideas may be placed within a five paragraph structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Paragraphs and Topic Sentences</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-7/</guid>
      <description>Paragraphs &amp;amp; Topic Sentences   I can remember picking up my father&amp;rsquo;s books before I could read. The words themselves were mostly foreign, but I still remember the exact moment when I first understood, with a sudden clarity, the purpose of a paragraph. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the vocabulary to say &amp;quot;paragraph,&amp;quot; but I realized that a paragraph was a fence that held words. The words inside a paragraph worked together for a common purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Working with Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>Working with Sources   The ugly fact is books are made out of books.
&amp;ndash;Cormac McCarthy
  Academic writing always involves integrating the thinking of others into your own writing. There are only three ways that the words and ideas of others may appear in your writing: summary, paraphrase, and quotation. Writing an academic paper requires a mastery of all three skills. It is critical to always give credit to the other authors whose ideas or words you borrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10. Plagiarism</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-10/</guid>
      <description>Plagiarism   Perish those who said our good things before we did.
&amp;ndash;Aelius Donatus
  Definition of plagiarism In the Academic Honor Principle, Dartmouth College defines plagiarism as
 the submission or presentation of work, in any form, that is not a student&amp;rsquo;s own, without acknowledgment of the source. With specific regard to papers, a simple rule dictates when it is necessary to acknowledge sources. If a student obtains information or ideas from an outside source, that source must be acknowledged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9. Altering Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-9/</guid>
      <description>Altering Sources  In your life as a writer you will frequently encounter situations where you must alter a source quotation in some way. Generally, these alterations are used to satisfy grammar or make your writing easier to follow by removing or adding words or phrases.
  To indicate that we have removed words from a source text we use ellipses . . . a series of periods to mark where something has been removed from the source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; FAQs</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/FAQs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/FAQs/</guid>
      <description>Course FAQs May I email you my essay for extra comments?  No. I always give each essay draft a full set of written comments. And I&amp;rsquo;m committed to meet with any student who would like to go over them. However, I usually do not take requests for extra comments via email unless there is no other possible way a student can meet with me in an office hour or at some other scheduled time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Research</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-12/</guid>
      <description>Academic Research  You are right to be wary. There is much bullshit. Be wary of me too, because I may be wrong. Make up your own mind after you evaluate all the evidence and logic.
&amp;mdash;Mark Rippetoe
  Research writing involves a number of important skills: library research, critical thinking, the evaluation of sources, and the ability to synthesize information through summary, paraphrase, and quotation. Although synthesizing the thinking of others is an important part of the research essay, in its true form the research essay strives for much more than a mere restatement of what others have said on a particular topic or question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Style</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-14/</guid>
      <description>On Style  I don&amp;rsquo;t usually talk about style with students, or teach it in any way. But some of the best advice on style I&amp;rsquo;ve ever read came from Gary Provost&amp;rsquo;s 100 Ways to Improve Your Writing:
 This sentence has five words. Here are five more words. Five-word sentences are fine. But several together become monotonous. Listen to what is happening. The writing is getting boring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11. Documentation of Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-11/</guid>
      <description>Documentation of Sources  Accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry. If you fail to properly document your sources, your readers will be unable to follow your research, validate your claims, or judge the quality of your argument. Furthermore, failing to properly cite a source (whether summarized, paraphrased, or quoted) opens you to the charge of plagiarism, a serious academic offense.
Scholars avoid plagiarism and give credit to the thinking and writing of others using a variety of citation formats, or &amp;ldquo;styles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Sentence Errors</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-13/</guid>
      <description>Common Sentence Errors  A statistical study of student writing performed in 1988 by scholars Andrea Lunsford and Robert Connors demonstrated that virtually 100% student writing mistakes are limited to 20 formal errors. Eliminating these errors in your writing therefore offers the quickest path to error-free prose.
1. Missing comma after an introductory element Introductory words or clauses are usually set off with a comma:
      Similarly Freire argues that memorization is dehumanizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I hate this too.
I&amp;rsquo;m not happy. You&amp;rsquo;re not happy. Let&amp;rsquo;s just try to use this time to prepare for the kinds of writing and research that you&amp;rsquo;ll want to do here at Dartmouth.
 Click as needed  The Course Sequence Writing 2-3 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The overarching objective of this course is to prepare you for the rigors of the academic life. To succeed in a scholarly environment we must develop good habits of inquiry, analysis, and communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Contact</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/about/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/about/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact    Email |  PGP
  PGP Fingerprint:
A14D 400A 810B CB92 F903
8773 035F 719F 2B4C 40F0
 Office   37 Dewey Field Road, room 224.
  TBA and by appointment.
 Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, my office hours for Fall 2020 will be held via Zoom.
Map  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note on using this text</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/using-this-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/using-this-text/</guid>
      <description>Using this Text I&amp;rsquo;ve created three types of highlighting or link styling in this text:
   Keyword Style Note     Keyword text A term you should know as a college student.   External links text A link to a resource or information outside this text.   Internal links text A topic covered in more depth located elsewhere within this text.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acknowledgments</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/acknowledgments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/acknowledgments/</guid>
      <description>Acknowledgments Thanks to my friends and colleagues at Dartmouth College&amp;mdash;especially Mark Koch, Doug Moody, Colleen Lannon, Sarah B. Smith, Jed Dobson, and Nick Van Kley.
Thanks also to the Dartmouth College Library and the Dartmouth Center for the Advancement of Learning who generously sponsored this Open Educational Resource project during the summer of 2019.
 This book is dedicated to Abel and Hayden.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annotation</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</guid>
      <description>Annotation  In college you will encounter demanding texts of great complexity. You will be asked to engage these texts critically and to challenge the thinking and conclusions of others. You will also have to retain an extraordinary amount of information and recall it later. To thrive in this environment, you will need to develop some new habits and strategies. The most basic, and most fundamental, of these is a formal procedure for the annotation of texts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Analysis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Analysis  Analysis involves breaking an argument down into smaller parts so that you can understand how those parts work together to make the whole. During this class we will try to train our minds to uncover the argumentative structure of all that we read. One of the most helpful tools for analysis is annotation&amp;mdash;the making of marks and symbols on the text itself.
Relying on your annotations, critical notes, and our discussions of the text, construct an outline of the argument found in Nicholson Baker&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Changes of Mind&amp;rdquo; essay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Summary</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</guid>
      <description>Argument Summary  In a summary you present the ideas of another writer in a condensed form. The length of a summary is dictated by your rhetorical needs, but they are always shorter than the original text. For example, the summary of a large book could be 20 pages, one paragraph, or one sentence. Although a summary sacrifices specificity and detail in the interest of brevity, it must always remain a faithful representation of the original text&amp;rsquo;s meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Synthesis  What is synthesis? As the name suggests, synthesis involves combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments relate to each another.
Students attempting synthesis for the first time often make the mistake of organizing their essays by source. For example, they will introduce two authors in their introduction, summarize Author A for a few paragraphs, summarize Author B for a few paragraphs, then conclude the essay by noting the broad similarities and differences in the two authors’ thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Documentation Style</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-11-chi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-11-chi/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Style  Chicago document formatting When setting up your word processor for an Chicago-formatted document, use the following settings to format your page:
Chicago Page Formatting    Use one-inch margins on all sides of the document.
  Place the page number on the right side of each page in the document&amp;rsquo;s header. If instructed to do so by a professor, include your last name before the page number on each page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Competencies in the Rhetorical Arts</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/core-competencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/core-competencies/</guid>
      <description>Core Competencies in the Rhetorical Arts  Many years ago, historian William Cronon described the ten characteristics of a &amp;ldquo;liberally educated&amp;rdquo; person. It&amp;rsquo;s a really good list. You should read it.
Here is my own list, focusing on the core competencies of the rhetorical arts. As I see it, the following are the most critical skills for successful writing and thinking in an academic context. None of these things is particularly easy to master, if such a thing is actually possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyword Index</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/keyword-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/keyword-index/</guid>
      <description>   Keyword Index This is a running list of the academic keywords and internal links within this text.
   Keyword Links     Altering Sources C8   Analysis C1, C6   Annotation C1   Archiving Work C4   Argument C6   Audience C3   Brackets [ ] C8   Chicago Style C11   Close Reading C1   Citation/Documentation C11   Ellipsis &amp;hellip; C8   Grammar C13   Highlighting C1   MLA Style C11   Note-taking C2   Organization C4, C7   Paragraphs C7   Paraphrase C8   Patchwriting C10   Peer Review WS   Plagiarism C7   Quotation C8   Research C12   Response C6   Signal Phrase C8   Sources C8, C9, C11   Summary C8    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLA Documentation Style</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-11-mla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/resources/open-handbook/chapter-11-mla/</guid>
      <description>MLA Style  MLA document formatting When setting up your word processor for an MLA-formatted document, use the following settings to format your page:
MLA Page Formatting   Set one-inch margins on all sides of the document.
  Double-space the entire document, including block quotes.
  In the top left portion of the first page, type your name, instructor&amp;rsquo;s name, course title, and date on separate, double-spaced lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Sentence Variety</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</guid>
      <description>Sentence Variety  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. Often, student writers who write sentences well in their own voice have difficulty when they try to weave the voices of others into their prose. I also find that most students have developed a particular strategy or formula for quotation that they use over and over again as a kind of crutch. In the recent batch of essays, I saw that many of you habitually rely on the same sentence structure when introducing a quotation from a source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>Peer Review Work  Step I: Make a basic outline Construct a brief outline of your partner&amp;rsquo;s essay by listing the main idea contained in each paragraph. Your focus should be on the paper&amp;rsquo;s argumentative structure, so concentrate on identifying the essay&amp;rsquo;s thesis and the supporting claims. Approach each paragraph as if it were a single unit of meaning. What claim does it make? What is its purpose?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</guid>
      <description>Altering sources  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. However, doing so is rarely a simple process of cutting and pasting the words from a source into your own document. Instead, you will routinely encounter challenges in the quotation of a source that threaten the clarity and correctness of your prose. For example:
  What do you do when you writing in the present tense and the source material you are quoting uses the past tense?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/working-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/working-sources/</guid>
      <description>Working with Sources Documentation, quotation, summary, paraphrase  Accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry. If you fail to properly document your sources, your readers will be unable to follow your research, validate your claims, or judge the quality of your argument. Furthermore, failing to cite a source (whether summarized, paraphrased or quoted) opens you to the charge of plagiarism, a serious academic offense.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>