<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 2</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 2  Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and articulating responses to them in the form of essays. Shorter writing assignments will focus on a number of skills that are important for taking part in academic conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay One</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1: Argument  What is education? What is its purpose? How does it shape us? Write an essay exploring these questions.
Format and length  No more than 3 pages Use the MLA format  Special requirement Do not perform any research for this essay. No googling. No library visits. Don’t ask your uncle, friends, or roommate. Just use your head and write what you think.
  Submit this assignment to Canvas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay Three</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</guid>
      <description>Essay Three: Theoretical Analysis  Max Fischer has an insatiable appetite for extracurricular activities: fencing, bee-keeping, yankee racers, calligraphy, backgammon, theater, and on and on and on. These projects and clubs are forms of self-improvement&amp;mdash;kinds of sovereign inquiry&amp;mdash;but they completely dwarf his responsibilities in the traditional disciplines of formal education: geometry, history, English, etc. According to Dr. Guggenheim, Max is &amp;ldquo;one of the worst students&amp;rdquo; at Rushmore Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay Two</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</guid>
      <description>Essay Two: Synthesis  Percy and Freire, each in their own way, ask us to consider the problem of authority within educational systems or experiences. Write an essay that synthesizes their thinking, explaining how they both investigate the nature of this problem, examine its consequences, and offer solutions.
As the name suggests, synthesis essays focus on combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments or ideas relate to one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Meet Your Professor   
Writing 2: What is Education? Course Description Prof&#39;s Current Jam 1  Prof&#39;s Current Jam 2  --- Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and articulating responses to them in the form of essays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus - OLD</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus-old/</guid>
      <description>Meet Your Professor   
Writing 2: What is Education? Course Description Prof&#39;s Current Jam 1  Prof&#39;s Current Jam 2  --- Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and articulating responses to them in the form of essays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 3</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 3  Writing 3 focuses on academic research writing. Our libraries have an impressive array of traditional and electronic search tools as well as millions of books, journal articles, and assorted media. Although navigating this vast sea of information is intimidating, it is important that you find your way: excellent research skills are fundamental to your undergraduate training, regardless of your chosen field of study. In consideration of its importance, we will spend a significant amount of time learning how to use our library effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>