<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What should students be able to do?</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/student-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/student-skills/</guid>
      <description>It seems such a simple question, especially given the frequency with which colleges and universities genuflect toward this well-worn phrase as the central icon of their institutional missions. Mantra-like, the words are endlessly repeated, starting in the glossy admissions brochures that high school students receive by the hundreds in their mailboxes and continuing right down to the last tired invocations they hear on commencement day. It would be surprising indeed if the phrase did not begin to sound at least a little empty after so much repetition, and surely undergraduates can be forgiven if they eventually regard liberal education as either a marketing ploy or a shibboleth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Obligatory COVID-19 Message:
The pandemic is total bullshit. We&amp;rsquo;re all struggling through this. But here we are. We might as well try to make the best of it.
 Use as required. --- Rage Button (NSFW)  --- Soothe Button  --- Therapy Button  --- Prof&#39;s Current Jam  # TODO - Get readings w/ embedded fonts: Baker, Percy, Freire. ---   Meet Your Professor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here is some shit about me and the class and the fucking pandemic shit we are facing. Writing is just goddamn hard. And it is much harder when you are alone and can&amp;rsquo;t connect with others to give you help. Email and Zoom are pretty fucking terrible substitutes. But, what are you gonna do? No way but through. With a mask.
I hate this too.
This pandemic is bullshit. I&amp;rsquo;m not happy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>