<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; FAQs</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/faq/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/faq/faq/</guid>
      <description>Course FAQs May I email you my essay for extra comments?  No. I usually do not take requests for extra comments via email unless there is no other possible way a student can meet with me in person. However, I am happy to discuss new drafts with students during office hours or at other times by appointment. Considering how easy it is to attach a file to an email, almost every student would seek this additional help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What should students be able to do?</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/student-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/student-skills/</guid>
      <description>What should students be able to do? Some years ago historian William Cronon asked &amp;ldquo;What does it mean to be a liberally educated person?&amp;rdquo; Cronon answers his own query by elaborating ten characteristics of the &amp;ldquo;liberally educated&amp;rdquo; person. It&amp;rsquo;s a really good list. You should read it.
Here is my own list, focusing on competencies and skills in the rhetorical arts:
  They analyze. Analysis involves breaking a complex thing down into smaller parts so that you can understand how those parts work together to make a whole (or fail to do so).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Obligatory COVID-19 Message:
The pandemic is total bullshit. We&amp;rsquo;re all struggling through this. But here we are. We might as well try to make the best of it.
 Use as required. --- Rage Button (NSFW)  --- Soothe Button  --- Therapy Button  --- Prof&#39;s Current Jam  # TODO - Get readings w/ embedded fonts: Baker, Percy, Freire. ---   Meet Your Professor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Here is some shit about me and the class and the fucking pandemic shit we are facing. Writing is just goddamn hard. And it is much harder when you are alone and can&amp;rsquo;t connect with others to give you help. Email and Zoom are pretty fucking terrible substitutes. But, what are you gonna do? No way but through. With a mask.
I hate this too.
This pandemic is bullshit. I&amp;rsquo;m not happy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>