<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 2</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 2  Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and articulating responses to them in the form of essays. Shorter writing assignments will focus on a number of skills that are important for taking part in academic conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End-of-term Reflection and Review</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/quarterly-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/quarterly-review/</guid>
      <description>Fall Reflection and Review This assignment takes the place of a final exam and asks you to reflect on all of your work this term. The reflections and self-evaluations you perform here will largely determine your final grade. Please write down your responses and keep them in a safe place&amp;mdash;they will be used in a conference during the first week of classes this winter term.
 My rationale for this assignment is explained somewhat in question #6 in the FAQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End-of-term Reflection and Review</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/quarterly-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/quarterly-review/</guid>
      <description>Winter Reflection and Review I. Review your participation  How many classes or TA sessions did you miss? How engaged were you in the class? Did you complete each of the 8 assigned lectures/workshops? Were your drafts completed and turned in on time? Did you give your best effort on each assignment? How much of the reading did you complete? Did you watch all of the films and prepare for discussion?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay One</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1: Argument  Prompt What is education? What is its purpose? Write an essay exploring these questions.
 No more than 3 pages   Use the MLA format   Special requirement Perform no research for this essay. No googling. No library visits. Don’t ask your uncle, friends, or roommate. Just use your head and write what you think (it will be ok).
  First Draft Notes  Topic Sentences and Unified Paragraphs  Topic Sentences Topic sentences function like a miniature thesis that communicates the purpose or main idea of a paragraph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay Three</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-3/</guid>
      <description>Essay Three: Theoretical Analysis Prompt Max Fischer has an insatiable appetite for extracurricular activities: fencing, bee-keeping, yankee racers, calligraphy, backgammon, theater, and on and on and on. These projects and clubs are forms of self-improvement&amp;mdash;kinds of sovereign inquiry&amp;mdash;but they completely dwarf his responsibilities in the traditional disciplines of formal education: geometry, history, English, etc. According to Dr. Guggenheim, Max is &amp;ldquo;one of the worst students&amp;rdquo; at Rushmore Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay Two</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-2/</guid>
      <description>Essay Two: Synthesis  Prompt Percy and Freire, each in their own way, ask us to consider the problem of authority that attends educational systems or the experience of learning. Write an essay that synthesizes their thinking, explaining how they both investigate the nature of this problem, examine its consequences, and offer solutions.
 Use the MLA format   On Synthesis As the name suggests, synthesis essays focus on combining and connecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the Post-Apocalyptic</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/post-apocalyptic-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/post-apocalyptic-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Ideas on the (Post)Apocalyptic  The post-apocalyptic narrative is a fantasy or species of wish-fulfillment that expresses a desire for the end of civilization as we know it. The popularity of such films and novels suggest a range of audience responses and psychological conditions behind this wish:    Economic despair and disempowering socio-economic structuring lead to a fanciful embrace of post-apocalyptic narrative as a balm, compensation, a comfort. We imagine a future where all systems of power, all hierarchies of values, all bureaucracies and governing institutions are utterly leveled, creating a landscape of pure possibility where anything is possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/wr2-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Syllabus   Meet Your Professor   ](/about/bio) --- Writing 2: Education and Authority Course Description Writing 2-3 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The course prepares you for work in a scholarly environment where you will be expected to engage in inquiry, perform analysis, and communicate clearly. We will cultivate these critical practices by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts, discussing them together, and composing responses to them in the form of essays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 3: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w21/</guid>
      <description>Post-apocalyptic Fiction, Film, and Art Course Description Why do we feel such an attraction to disaster? Why do we produce novels, films, and other forms of art that contemplate the end of humanity? Scholars from many disciplines have offered theories about the appeal and meaning of such spectacles of apocalyptic destruction. We will read some of this critical literature, examining views from disciplines such as psychology, sociology, cultural studies, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 3: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus-w22/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Syllabus    Post-apocalyptic Fiction, Film, and Art Course Description Why do we feel such an attraction to disaster? Why do we produce novels, films, and other forms of art that contemplate the end of humanity? Scholars from many disciplines have offered theories about the appeal and meaning of such spectacles of apocalyptic destruction. We will read some of this critical literature, examining views from disciplines such as psychology, sociology, cultural studies, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 3: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/old-syllabi/wr3-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Syllabus    Post-apocalyptic Fiction, Film, and Art Course Description Why do we feel such an attraction to disaster? Why do we produce novels, films, and other forms of art that contemplate the end of humanity? Scholars from many disciplines have offered theories about the appeal and meaning of such spectacles of apocalyptic destruction. We will read some of this critical literature, examining views from disciplines such as psychology, sociology, cultural studies, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 3: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/wr3-syllabus-alt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/wr3-syllabus-alt/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Syllabus   Post-apocalyptic Fiction, Film, and Art Course Description Why do we feel such an attraction to disaster? Why do we produce novels, films, and other forms of art that contemplate the end of humanity? Scholars from many disciplines have offered theories about the appeal and meaning of such spectacles of apocalyptic destruction. We will read some of this critical literature, examining views from disciplines such as psychology, sociology, cultural studies, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 3</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 3  Writing 3 focuses on academic research writing. Our libraries have an impressive array of traditional and electronic search tools as well as millions of books, journal articles, and assorted media. Although navigating this vast sea of information is intimidating, it is important that you find your way: excellent research skills are fundamental to your undergraduate training, regardless of your chosen field of study. In consideration of its importance, we will spend a significant amount of time learning how to use our library effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aphorisms on the Post-Apocalyptic</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/observations-on-apocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/observations-on-apocalypse/</guid>
      <description>Observations on the Post-Apocalyptic A collection of random thoughts on the post-apocalyptic narrative:
 The post-apocalyptic narrative is a fantasy or species of wish-fulfillment that expresses a desire for the end of civilization as we know it. The popularity of such films suggest a range of audience responses and psychological conditions behind this wish:    1a. Economic despair and disempowering socio-economic structuring lead to a fanciful embrace of post-apocalyptic narrative as a balm, compensation, a comfort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Author Page Example</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/author-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/author-page/</guid>
      <description>This is a mockup of an Author Page for a research project. Use this as a template for your own project. Create your own Author Page as a Google doc; or, if you prefer, you may use the Journeys WordPress platform. Put a link to your project on our course research projects page.   Alan Taylor Revanchist Masculinity in Recent Post-Apocalyptic Cinema This paper examines a strain of post-apocalyptic narrative featuring what we may call “revanchist masculinity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Notes</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/reading-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/reading-notes/</guid>
      <description>Disaster, Apocalypse, and the State of Nature Reading Notes Thomas Hobbes, Leviathan (1651)  Men are essentially equal when all is “reckoned together.” Equal in power, equal in common sense or wisdom. We might think that we are smarter than others, but we are mostly the same.  This sense of equality leads to three causes of &amp;ldquo;quarrel&amp;rdquo;:
  COMPETITION: Because we know ourselves to be equals, we become hopeful of attaining ends, goals, possessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stills from Night of the Living Dead</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/night-stills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/night-stills/</guid>
      <description>Stills from Night of the Living Dead (1968)  Review of Night of the Living Dead by film critic Roger Ebert (1969):   &amp;ldquo;The kids in the audience were stunned. There was almost complete silence. The movie had stopped being delightfully scary about halfway through, and had become unexpectedly terrifying. There was a little girl across the aisle from me, maybe nine years old, who was sitting very still in her seat and crying.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
