<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 2</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 2  Writing 2 is an introduction to academic writing. The course focuses on how to acquire knowledge, evaluate evidence, think critically, synthesize information, and make effective arguments. We will cultivate these critical practices through rigorous group inquiry&amp;mdash; by reading and analyzing a series of demanding texts and responding to them in the form of essays. Shorter writing assignments and workshops will focus on a number of skills that are important for taking part in academic conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay One</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1 Assignment  What is education? What is its purpose? Write an essay exploring these questions.
Format and length  No more than 3 pages. MLA format.  Special requirement Do not perform any research for this essay. No googling. No library visits. Don’t ask your uncle, friends, or roommate. Just use your head and write what you think.
Submission     Submit this assignment to Canvas.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/test/</guid>
      <description>Outside of the tabs environment, this works as expected:
    Question of the Day: Something you love/hate?  But inside tabs environment, this breaks the line:
9.14 Course orientation  Item one Item two    This is a test. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing 2: Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-2/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Obligatory COVID-19 Message:
The pandemic is total bullshit. We&amp;rsquo;re all struggling through this. But here we are. We might as well try to make the best of it.
 Use as required. --- Rage Button (NSFW)  --- Soothe Button  --- Therapy Button  --- Prof&#39;s Current Jam  # TODO - Get readings w/ embedded fonts: Baker, Percy, Freire. ---   Meet Your Professor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#43; Writing 3</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/course-description/</guid>
      <description>Writing 3  Writing 3 focuses on academic research writing. Our libraries have an impressive array of traditional and electronic search tools as well as millions of books, journal articles, and assorted media. Although navigating this vast sea of information is intimidating, it is important that you find your way: excellent research skills are fundamental to your undergraduate training, regardless of your chosen field of study. In consideration of its importance, we will spend a significant amount of time learning how to use our library effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/writing-3/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I hate this too.
I&amp;rsquo;m not happy. You&amp;rsquo;re not happy. Let&amp;rsquo;s just try to use this time to prepare for the kinds of writing and research that you&amp;rsquo;ll want to do here at Dartmouth.
 Click as needed  The Course Sequence Writing 2-3 is an introduction to academic writing and research. The overarching objective of this course is to prepare you for the rigors of the academic life. To succeed in a scholarly environment we must develop good habits of inquiry, analysis, and communication.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>