<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshops on No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshops on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Annotation</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</guid>
      <description>Annotation  In college you will encounter demanding texts of great complexity. You will be asked to engage these texts critically and to challenge the thinking and conclusions of others. You will also have to retain an extraordinary amount of information and recall it later. To thrive in this environment you will need to develop some new habits and strategies. The most basic, and most fundamental, of these is a formal procedure for the annotation of texts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Analysis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Analysis  Analysis involves breaking an argument down into smaller parts so that you can understand how those parts work together to make the whole (or fail to do so). During this class we will try to train our minds to uncover the argumentative structure of all that we read.
Workshop Relying on your annotations and critical notes, construct an outline of the argument found in Nicholson Baker&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Changes of Mind&amp;rdquo; essay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Summary</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</guid>
      <description>Argument Summary  In a summary you present the ideas of another writer in condensed form. The length of a summary is dictated by your rhetorical needs, but they are always shorter than the original text. For example, the summary of a large book could be 20 pages, one paragraph, or one sentence. Although a summary sacrifices specificity and detail in the interest of brevity, it must always remain a faithful representation of the original text&amp;rsquo;s meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Synthesis  What is synthesis? As the name suggests, synthesis involves combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments relate to each another.
Students attempting synthesis for the first time often make the mistake of organizing their essays by source. For example, they will introduce two authors in their introduction, summarize Author A for a few paragraphs, summarize Author B for a few paragraphs, then conclude the essay by noting the broad similarities and differences in the two authors’ thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Sentence Variety</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</guid>
      <description>Sentence Variety  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. Student writers are often able to write sentences well in their own voice but have difficulty when they try to weave the voices of others into their prose. I also find that most students have developed a particular strategy or formula for quotation that they use over and over again as a kind of crutch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>Peer Review Work  Reflective Prologue Take a moment to reflect on your work. Consider the following questions and write answers to them at the conclusion of your essay draft. Please ensure that this reflective work appears in the essay draft you turn in to Canvas as well.
 What did you learn by writing this draft? What was the most challenging thing about creating this draft? What do you like most about this draft?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</guid>
      <description>Altering sources  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. However, doing so is rarely a simple process of cutting and pasting the words from a source into your own document. Instead, you will routinely encounter challenges during the quotation of a source that threaten the clarity and correctness of your prose. For example:
   What do you do when you are writing in the present tense and the source material you are quoting uses the past tense?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/working-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/working-sources/</guid>
      <description>Working with Sources Documentation, quotation, summary, paraphrase  Perhaps the most challenging aspect of academic writing is the integration of source materials. Students often imagine that the most difficult thing about using sources is learning how and when to use a citation. While accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry, citing the page number of a source is not the only skill that is required.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
