<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshops on No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshops on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Altering Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops  Altering sources  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. However, doing so is rarely a simple process of cutting and pasting the words from a source into your own document. Instead, you will routinely encounter challenges during the quotation of a source that threaten the clarity and correctness of your prose. For example:
   What do you do when you are writing in the present tense and the source material you are quoting uses the past tense?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annotation</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops  Annotation  In college you will encounter demanding texts of great complexity. You will be asked to engage these texts critically and to challenge the thinking and conclusions of others. You will also have to retain an extraordinary amount of information and recall it later. To thrive in this environment you will need to develop some new habits and strategies. The most basic, and most fundamental, of these is a formal procedure for the annotation of texts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Analysis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops  Argument Analysis  Analysis involves breaking an argument down into smaller parts so that you can understand how those parts work together to make the whole (or fail to do so). During this class we will try to train our minds to uncover the argumentative structure of all that we read.
Workshop Relying on your annotations and critical notes, construct an outline of the argument found in Nicholson Baker&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Changes of Mind&amp;rdquo; essay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Summary</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops  Argument Summary  In a summary you present the ideas of another writer in condensed form. The length of a summary is dictated by your rhetorical needs, but they are always shorter than the original text. For example, the summary of a large book could be 20 pages, one paragraph, or one sentence. Although a summary sacrifices specificity and detail in the interest of brevity, it must always remain a faithful representation of the original text&amp;rsquo;s meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Synthesis  What is synthesis? As the name suggests, synthesis involves combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments relate to each another.
Students attempting synthesis for the first time often make the mistake of organizing their essays by source. For example, they will introduce two authors in their introduction, summarize Author A for a few paragraphs, summarize Author B for a few paragraphs, then conclude the essay by noting the broad similarities and differences in the two authors’ thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bibliographic Management</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/bibliographic-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/bibliographic-management/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Bibliographic Management Most of us take a very shortsighted approach to our work. We take notes. We do the readings. We complete the assignments. We turn in our work and receive our grade. But then we just move on. All the work product from our labors and the materials we used for learning are abandoned; ultimately, they cross the event horizon into the black hole of a computer hard drive, never to emerge again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting Corners</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/cutting-corners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/cutting-corners/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Cutting Corners in Research I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you the number of times a first-year student has waited until the other students left the classroom in order to sheepishly approach me ask this question: &amp;ldquo;Professor, if I get a book from the library or download an article for my research project, do I have to read the whole thing?&amp;rdquo;
Don&amp;rsquo;t be silly; of course not.
And I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you a secret: professors don&amp;rsquo;t read everything in their field(s) of study either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding a Book in the Library</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/locate-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/locate-books/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Finding a Book in the Library Finding a book (or other physical resource) on the shelf of the library isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as it sounds. This is a guide to help you understand how libraries are organized and find books you need for your research.
Library Classification Systems Libraries use classification systems to organize their holdings. The most common in the English-speaking world are the Dewey Decimal Classification (DDC) and the Library of Congress Classification (LCC) systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Periodicals</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/find-periodicals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/find-periodicals/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Finding Periodicals &amp;amp; Electronic Databases  Periodicals are publications that are published at regular intervals, such as scholarly journals, magazines, and newspapers. Examining periodicals&amp;mdash;especially academic journals&amp;mdash;is an important aspect of research. Since books often take a year or more to go through the process of peer review, editing, typesetting, and printing before they become available for purchase, they often do not contain the most current information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Books/Articles We Don&#39;t Own</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/inter-library-loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/inter-library-loan/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Getting Sh*t the Library Doesn&amp;rsquo;t Have A common problem in academic research is discovering that a book or article you require for a project is checked out, missing, or not owned by the library. Less commonly, you may find yourself in a global pandemic and be unable to physically visit a library to borrow books. There are a number of free services available to you when you encounter this problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Academic Research</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/academic-research-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/academic-research-intro/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Introduction to Academic Research  &amp;ldquo;The problem is that doing scholarly work is intrinsically a mess.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; Kieran Healy
 Perhaps the most common feature of books designed to help students do academic research is their dishonesty. These textbooks present academic research as an orderly list of procedures and tasks, each one leading logically to the next, culminating in a superbly crafted essay. This narrative generally begins with the formulation of a research question, proceeds to the gathering of background information and secondary sources, and finally to the drafting, revision, and completion of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Cultural Studies</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/cultural-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/cultural-studies/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Introduction to Cultural Studies This class will frequently use a mode of analysis associated with cultural studies. This lecture provides a brief (and wholly reductive) introduction to this form of inquiry.
  Further reading and citations:   Completely optional further reading on cultural studies and related concepts:  &amp;ldquo;Cultural Studies,&amp;quot;, by Dan Kagan;  &amp;ldquo;Articulation Theory,&amp;quot; by Jennifer Daryl Slack; and  &amp;ldquo;Cultural Materialism,&amp;quot; by Macdonald Daly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Sentence Variety</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Sentence Variety  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. Student writers are often able to write sentences well in their own voice but have difficulty when they try to weave the voices of others into their prose. I also find that most students have developed a particular strategy or formula for quotation that they use over and over again as a kind of crutch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching with Precision</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/search-with-precision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/search-with-precision/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops    Searching with Precision This workshop is designed to help you perform keyword searches of library catalogs and electronic databases with efficiency. While most students have some familiarity with keyword searching through the Google search engine, library catalogs and databases don&amp;rsquo;t work in the same way. To query databases effectively and efficiently, you need to be familiar with Boolean searches.
Keyword searches often produce too many results to examine in a reasonable amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops  Peer Review Work  Reflective Prologue Take a moment to reflect on your work. Consider the following questions and write answers to them at the conclusion of your essay draft. Please ensure that this reflective work appears in the essay draft you turn in to Canvas as well.
 What did you learn by writing this draft? What was the most challenging thing about creating this draft?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Peer Review?</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-reviews/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Peer review Peer review is a form of quality control in academic publishing. Before books or articles are published, they experience a rigorous process of evaluation by at least three experts who have advanced training in the field of study in question. These &amp;ldquo;referees,&amp;rdquo; as they are known, review the work anonymously. This anonymity theoretically ensures a more honest appraisal of the work under consideration for publication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/working-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/working-sources/</guid>
      <description>WR2 | Workshops  Working with Sources Documentation, quotation, summary, paraphrase  Perhaps the most challenging aspect of academic writing is the integration of source materials. Students often imagine that the most difficult thing about using sources is learning how and when to use a citation. While accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry, citing the page number of a source is not the only skill that is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works Cited / Bibliography</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/chicago-bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/chicago-bibliography/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Works Cited or Bibliography Accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry. If you fail to properly document your sources, your readers will be unable to follow your research, validate your claims, or judge the quality of your argument. Furthermore, failing to properly cite a source (whether summarized, paraphrased, or quoted) opens you to the charge of plagiarism, a serious academic offense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works Cited / Bibliography</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/mla-bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/mla-bibliography/</guid>
      <description>WR3 | Workshops  Works Cited or Bibliography Accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry. If you fail to properly document your sources, your readers will be unable to follow your research, validate your claims, or judge the quality of your argument. Furthermore, failing to properly cite a source (whether summarized, paraphrased, or quoted) opens you to the charge of plagiarism, a serious academic offense.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
