<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>&#43; Workshops on No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in &#43; Workshops on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Annotation</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/annotation/</guid>
      <description>Annotation  Not yet. Hold on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Analysis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Analysis  Relying on your annotations, critical notes, and our discussions of the text, construct an outline of the argument found in Nicholson Baker&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Changes of Mind&amp;rdquo; essay.
Your focus in this assignment is on the essay&amp;rsquo;s argumentative structure. What is the main conclusion that Baker wants you to accept? We can call this central claim his thesis. What other supporting claims does he make to bolster this conclusion?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Summary</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</guid>
      <description>Argument Summary  Write a summary of Nicholson Baker’s argument in “Changes of Mind” that is no more than 250 words.
Include all of Baker’s argumentative claims or assertions. Leave nothing out. Put nothing extra in. Remain objective: don&amp;rsquo;t tell the audience your opinions or how you feel about Baker&amp;rsquo;s writing or argument. Just give us the facts.
  Don’t forget to provide MLA-formatted citations indicating the page number(s) of the points you summarize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Synthesis  What is synthesis? As the name suggests, synthesis involves combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments relate to each another.
Students attempting synthesis for the first time often make the mistake of organizing their essays by source. For example, they will introduce two authors in their introduction, summarize Author A for a few paragraphs, summarize Author B for a few paragraphs, then conclude the essay by noting the broad similarities and differences in the two authors’ thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLA Documentation</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/documentation/</guid>
      <description>MLA Documentation  Accurately documenting sources is a vital aspect of any process of inquiry. If you fail to properly document your sources, your readers will be unable to follow your research, validate your claims, or judge the quality of your argument. Furthermore, failing to cite a source (whether summarized, paraphrased or quoted) opens you to the charge of plagiarism, a serious academic offense. With this in mind, it is vital that you become acquainted with how to document sources in your writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Sentence Variety</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/sentence-variety/</guid>
      <description>Sentence Variety  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. Often, student writers who write sentences well in their own voice have difficulty when they try to weave the voices of others into their prose. I also find that most students have developed a particular strategy or formula for quotation that they use over and over again as a kind of crutch. In the recent batch of essays, I saw that many of you habitually rely on the same sentence structure when introducing a quotation from a source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>Peer Review Work  Step I: Make a basic outline Construct a brief outline of your partner&amp;rsquo;s essay by listing the main idea contained in each paragraph. Your focus should be on the paper&amp;rsquo;s argumentative structure, so concentrate on identifying the essay&amp;rsquo;s thesis and the supporting claims. Approach each paragraph as if it were a single unit of meaning. What claim does it make? What is its purpose?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Sources</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/altering-sources/</guid>
      <description>Altering sources  Integrating quotations from other sources is an important part of academic writing. However, doing so is rarely a simple process of cutting and pasting the words from another source into your document. For example:
  What do you do when you writing in the present tense and the source material you are quoting uses the past tense?
  What if the sentence you want to quote contains extraneous words or phrases that are a distraction from your intended purpose?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>