<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>&#43; Workshops on No Silo</title>
    <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in &#43; Workshops on No Silo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Analysis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Analysis  Relying on your annotations, critical notes, and our discussions of the text, construct an outline of the argument found in Nicholson Baker&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Changes of Mind&amp;rdquo; essay.
Your focus in this assignment is on the essay&amp;rsquo;s argumentative structure. What is the main conclusion that Baker wants you to accept? We can call this central claim his thesis. What other claims does he make to support this conclusion?
Baker is a very playful writer; there is a lot of silliness and verbal excess in the essay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Summary</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-summary/</guid>
      <description>Argument Summary Workshop  Write a summary of Nicholson Baker’s argument in “Changes of Mind” that is no more than 250 words.
Include all of Baker’s argumentative claims or assertions. Leave nothing out. Put nothing extra in. Remain objective: don&amp;rsquo;t tell the audience your opinions or how you feel about Baker&amp;rsquo;s writing or argument. Just give us the facts.
  Don’t forget to provide MLA-formatted citations indicating the page number(s) of the points you summarize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argument Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/argument-synthesis/</guid>
      <description>Argument Synthesis  What is synthesis? As the name suggests, synthesis involves combining and connecting. Your focus in a synthesis essay is to explain to your audience the ways in which two or more arguments relate to each another.
Students attempting synthesis for the first time often make the mistake of organizing their essays by source. For example, they will introduce two authors in their introduction, summarize Author A for a few paragraphs, summarize Author B for a few paragraphs, then conclude the essay by noting the broad similarities and differences in the two authors’ thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://no-silo.com/courses/workshops/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>Peer Review Work Step I: Make a basic outline Construct a brief outline of your partner&amp;rsquo;s essay by listing the main idea contained in each paragraph. Your focus should be on the paper&amp;rsquo;s argumentative structure, so concentrate on identifying the essay&amp;rsquo;s thesis and the supporting claims. Approach each paragraph as if it were a single unit of meaning. For the moment, the paragraph is all that exists: what claim does it make?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>